"嘿，嘿，嘿......这是美林和吉尔在做他们最喜欢的工作."
"Hey, hey, hey... this is Mele and Jill doing
their favorite work, their calling. "
女孩们，这很适合你们，可比走秀好得多。你们应该开始摆几个姿势，或许能带来野营所需的经费。
Girls, this suits you much better than the catwalk.
Maybe you should start advertising for camping requirements.
来吧，给我一个微笑......
Come on, give me a smile...
这可怕的天气，是吧？
This is awesome weather, isn't it?
我们应拿一些......他妈的，现在我们要进行所有的野营准备。
We should have picked up some guys...
Now we have to carry all that shit on our own.
大丽花，你能放下摄像机帮助我们吗？
Dahlia, would you put down the camera
and start helping us?
就现在。
Now.
你习惯了摄像机拍摄，别悲伤，如果你努力，就能成为你一生的事业。
You are used to cameras and again, don't cry
if you have to work hard for once in your lifetime.
停下。你不知道什么才是摄像。
Stop it. You don't know what real work is like.
嗯，我们终于完成。接下来做什么？
Well, we are finally done. What shall we do
until the others arrive?
酒在哪里？
Where is the wine?
小吃在哪？我饿了...-大丽花，别吃太多。你的肚子不适合......
Where are the snacks? I'm getting hungry... -
Dahlia, stop eating so much. Your ass won't fit in...
嘿，嘿，让我们开始我们的宴会 ！
Hey, hey, let's start the party!
没有落在我身上，也不在摄像机上 ！
Not on me, not on the camera!
啊，好了，这成什么样子了。好吧，女孩。
Ah okay, that's what it looks like.
All right, girls.
想要一些吗?
Do you want some, too?
那是什么?
What was that?
这就是答案----好东西。
That was the answer to good shit.
我什么也没听到。
I don't hear anything.
好像有什么东西。
There is something.
在哪里？
Where is it?
正站在灌木丛里，盯着看我们。来吧，你这个愚蠢的笨蛋 ！这是私人聚会的地方 ！
They are standing in the bushes and staring.
Come out, you stupid fuckers! This is a private party here!
美林？美林，回来，我们离开。
Mele? Mele, come on, let's leave.
我没看到什么。
I don't see anything.
想要看奶子吗？我会给你看 ！
Wanna see tits? I will get you some!
美林，回来，你不知道谁在那里。
Mele, come on, you don't know who is out there.
回来！
Come back!
出来，他妈的混蛋 ！
Get out you fucking bastards!
妈的，又熄火了。
Damn, the engine died again.
太好了！现在怎么办？
Great! And now?
修好它吗？
Repair?
我们拿出袋子。
Let's take out the bags.
我拿扳手。
Get me the wrench.
这件吗？-是的。
This one? -
One moment.
嗨 sweew
Hey sweew-
嘿，怎么样了?
Hey, how is it going?
我们的车有一个小故障，但我们会准时到达。你怎么样了?
We've had a little break-down, but we will arrive
on time. What's up with you?
我现在已经完成了工作模型。这令人敬畏。我要告诉你，很快。
I have finished the model job now.
It was awesome. I need to tell you about that soon.
我在打扮，然后我会满足你们。
I'm dressing myself up and then I will meet you guys later.
不是这个，另一个 ！我不认为你的小妹妹将会成为一个技工。
Not this one, the other one!
I don't think your little sister will become a mechanic.
嘿，别对她吝啬。你能让她听电话吗？
Hey, don't be mean to her.
Could you get her the phone for a second?
当然可以。
Sure.
喂？
Hello?
甜心生日快乐 ！你收到礼物了吗?
Happy birthday sweety! Did you get the present?
是的。真是太好了。我很喜欢它。
Yes. It is very nice. I really like it.
我很抱歉昨天没能去你那儿。但我们今天会给你庆祝，好吗？
I'm sorry that I couldn't be there yesterday.
But we'll make it up today, okay?
哦，太棒了。酷毙了。
Oh, that's going to be awesome. Cool.
席琳？先不要告诉塔尼娅，好吗？
And Celine? Do not put up with everything
Tanja says, okay?
不，我不会这样做
No, I won't do that.
很好。回头见。
Great. See you later.
再见。-好了，我修好了。过来收拾东西。
Bye. -
Okay, we are finished now. Come on and pack the stuff up.
操。
Fuck.
来吧，捡起来。
Come on, pick it up.
嘿，Celine，是我。我有一个问题。我迷失了方向，我在荒郊野外。
Hey Celine, it's me. I have a problem. I lost myway
and I am in the middle of nowhere.
你告诉塔尼娅给我回电话？好的，谢谢你。
Could you tell Tanja to call me back?
Okay thanks, see you.
对不起？
Excuse me?
对不起，你能帮我吗？
Excuse me, can you help me?
我失去了方向，我也不知道我在哪里。你可以帮我吗？
I lost myway and I have no idea where I am.
Can you help me?
你们城里人...你看不懂简单的地图真是太愚蠢了。
You city slickers... you are too stupid to read a simple map.
你能不能帮我？
Can you help me or not?
当然可以。
Yes, sure.
我也不知道您打算去哪里，但你在这里是错了。
Well, I have no idea where you are planning to go to,
but you are wrong here.
该死 ！现在怎么办？
Damn! And now?
听着，好吗?你回头看，开车去那边一条道？
Listen, okay? You turn around and drive back
to the crossroadspkay?
到那里你右转，然后直走继续开车。
And there you turn right and then keep driving straight ahead.
你将开车经过禁区。
You will get to a restricted area where you just drive through.
禁区？
Restricted area?
明白了？要开车穿过禁区。
Got it? Just drive through the restricted area.
你说的是什么？
What are you talking about?
那是一家污染多年来的工厂。
The factories. They contaminated everything over the years.
但有一个工厂...一个...以前在那儿发生化学品事故。
But there was one factory... one...
where they had accidents with chemicals and stuff all the time.
有人说，员工疯了，是因为化学气体导致的。
Some say, that the employees went nuts because of
vapors and killed themselves in the end.
好
Okay"-
像你这种可爱的小东西应该迅速开车穿过那个地方。
And such a sweet little thing like you should
drive through that place quickly.
所以当你通过时，应该做个深呼吸。
So you guys should take a deep breath when you pass through.
什么样的家伙？
What guys?
那辆车上是你的朋友吗？
You and your friend in that car?
什么？
What?
嘿 ！
Hey!
他妈的 ！混蛋 ！
Fuck! Asshole!
我们到了。
So here we are.
这是在哪里？
And this is the location?
你看到在那里的女孩们的帐篷。来吧，我们稍后把行李取下来。
Sure, you can see the girls' tents over there.
Come on, we will get the bags later.
来吧！
Come on!
来...
Coming...
女孩 ！在哪里？
Girls! Where are you?
你确定是这地方？
Are you sure this is the right place?
肯定是的。这些都是他们的帐篷。
Of course. These are their tents.
妈的，肯定是的，他们还在这里。
Damn sure, they were here.
好吧，我没看到这里有任何人。
Well, I don't see anyone here.
禁区，污染危险，不能进入
RESTRICTED AREA RISK OF
CONTAMINATION DO NOT ENTER
等等。
Wait.
有铃声。
It's ringing.
美林的手机。
It's Mele's cell phone.
她去哪儿了呢？
Why did she leave it here?
喂？
Hello?
有人吗?
Is someone here?
我打电话给卡蒂。
I call Kati.
卡蒂？喂？
Kati? Hello?
发生了什么事？
What happened?
我不知道。
I don't know.
该死的。-拜托，别出什么事。
Damn. -
Come on, there is something wrong.
有人吗？
Hello?
妈的。
Shit.
你看，那边有张地图。
Look, the map over there.
这是卡蒂的地图。
That is Kati's map.
真的吗？-是的，她来过这里。来吧，我们看一看。
Really? - Yes, she must have been here before.
Come on, let's have a look.
她为什么会孤自去树林里?-我不知道。我们找找。
But why would she go in the woods alone?-
I have no clue. Let's check it out.
卡蒂？
Kati?
卡蒂，你在哪里吗？
Kati, where are you?
有人吗？
Hello?
卡蒂？
Kati?
那是什么？
What's that?
他妈的 ！
Fuck!
这不是真的。为什么锁住了门？
That can't be true. Why is everything locked?
妈的!
Nu!
他妈的。
Shit.
妈的!
Fuck it!
他妈的。
Shit.
卡蒂！
Kati!
我累了。
I'm tired.
听着，我们已经在附近走了几个小时，我想她不在这里。
Listen, we've been walking around for hours
and I don't think she's here.
我觉得她在这里的某个地方，这样吧，
我们分头去找可能更快地找到她，这是最好的办法。
Well, I think she's here somewhere.
It would be the best if we split up to find her quicker.
我们不能分开找！我怕会像在那些恐怖片里的事情要发生。
We can't split up! Hello, it's just like
in all those scary movies... something will happen.
别这样懦弱，你是一个成年人 ！你走这条路我走那条路，在五分钟后我们在这里见面。
Don't be such a coward, you're an adult! You go this way,
I go that way and in five minutes we meet up again right here.
如果发生什么事，你可以叫我。
You can call me if something happens.
卡蒂！
Kati!
该死的森林 ！
God damn forest!
卡蒂！
Kati!
卡蒂？
Kati?
卡蒂，是你吗？
Celine, is that you?
卡蒂？
Kati?
卡蒂？你在哪里？
Kati? Where are you?
我不害怕......妈的！
I'm not scared... Shit!
塔尼娅！
Tanja!
我要快点，快点离开 ！
I need to hurry up, I need to get away!
他妈的 ！
Fuck!
妈的...
Dammit...
这是什么？
What's this?
你想要什么？
What do you want?
制造！
Make'.!
哦，上帝 ！
Oh God!
制造！
Make'.!
您是我的新妈咪吗？
Are you our new mommy?
什么？
What?
你是我新的妈咪吗？
You are our new mommy, aren't you?
不，我不是你的新妈妈。
No, I'm not your new mommy.
你是我的新妈妈，直到下一个来临！
You are our new mommy, 'till the next one arrives!
放开我！
Let mg go!
别碰我，你这个混蛋 ！
Hands off me, you bastard!
他妈的 ！
Fuck!
嘿-
Hey-
我有更好的东西给你。
I've got something better for you.
我猜你从未见过像我这样一个性感的女孩在您的相机前裸体，对不对？
I guess you have never seen a sexy girl like me
naked in front of your camera, right?
嘿 ！
Hey!
表演完了 ！
The show is over!
王八蛋。
Motherfucker.
我如何把这东西打开？
How do I turn this thing on?
...不 ！该死 ！
...not! Damn!
为什么会没有出口？
Why is there no exit?
出口在哪里？
Where is the exit?